# Openiyi Ibrahim

UX/UI Developer Graphics Designer Web Developer Frontend Developer

A Professional Designer and Developer with more than three and a half years of experience in the Business Design, Development process, Management, and Development of new Business ideas & Opportunities.



Openiyiibrahim@gmail.com



+2348157062795



Accra, Ghana.



Openiyi ibrahim

### CAREER OBJECTIVE

To join an ambitious organization to contribute my skills and experience to its goals and build myself in the field.

### **SKILLS**

HTML & CSS, JavaScript, React, MongoDB, Adobe XD, Figma, Adobe illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Empathy, Brand Strategy, Research & Strategy, Emotional Intelligence, Leadership, Analytical and organizational, Training & Development, Microsoft Office Proficiency, Graphics Design Proficiency, Creativity, Apt Verbal & Written Communication, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Decision Making.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Robbin Michael

Web Technology Specialist

(December 2017 - August 2018)

Lagos Nigeria

Setting up workstations with computers and necessary peripheral devices

- Writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices.
- Creating website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS practices.
- ❖ Create and maintain software documentation.
- responsible for maintaining, expanding, and scaling site
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical need.
- Installing and configuring appropriate software and functions according to specifications
- Creating a wide range of graphics and layouts for product illustrations, company logos, and websites with software such as Photoshop.
- \* Reviewing final layouts and suggesting improvements when necessary.
- ❖ Acting as a contact between the company and its potential and existing markets.
- ❖ Maintain and develop relationships with existing customers.
- Presenting the product favorably and in a structured professional way face-to-face.

### Ariana Diaries

Graphics Designer

(August 2018 - 2021)

Sierra Leone, Nigeria

- ❖ Planning concepts by studying relevant information and materials.
- ❖ Illustrating concepts by designing examples of art arrangement, size, type size and style and submitting them for approval.
- Preparing finished art by operating necessary equipment and software.

- Coordinating with outside agencies, art services, web designer, marketing, printers, and colleagues as necessary.
- ❖ Contributing to team efforts by accomplishing tasks as needed.
- ❖ Communicating with clients about layout and design.

# (NYSC) Jofame Integrated Limited Information Technology Development Intern (January 2017 - December 2017)

Lagos, Nigeria

- ❖ Provide orientation and guidance to users on how to operate new software and computer equipment.
- Develop and maintain local networks in ways that optimize performance.
- ❖ Ensure security and privacy of networks and computer systems.
- Perform troubleshooting to diagnose and resolve problems (repair or replace parts, debugging etc.
- Identify computer or network equipment shortages and place orders.

### **EDUCATION**

B.Sc.Ed Educational Technology University of Ilorin, Kwara State. (2012 - 2017)

### HOBBIES

- Coding
- ❖ Reading Books and Articles
- Cooking and baking
- ❖ Solving Puzzle Games
- Travelling

# LANGUAGES

English (Full Professional Proficiency) Yoruba (Native or Bilingual Proficiency)

## REFEREES

Mr. Idris Adisa +234 806 665 8741